sup everyone 1085 here with a very
special video today no I mean wama
looking for ingredients meeting my
special sock coming out cookies that
make every weekend and and I
thought hey you know what what I'm here
while I'm out looking for Vince how
about put together video some
and so I thought this video will be
about addressing a question that I see
people talk about every single day
whether it be on YouTube or the stock
photo some and that is where the
is battle because as you all know
Bobby is on this is rough on me
yeah get out my way
well anyways damn when he the
thing up Bobby is what we don't know is
Bobby he is an exclusive soccer on
character what makes suck Underground so
good is that it has such great
characters that they can't other series
can only dream of having and Bobby you
you just can't beat that the golden half
the hourglass figure of a big ass book
speaking of his ba funny story
thorn history when I first saw up all of
me
my parents they walked and they said
who's that character
I called him big boy I said that's big
but up there on the screen and
it's because he had such a big bud like
I knew his name was Bobby but damn his
his his big ass is all that was in my
mind at the time no kind of silly should
I get maybe with a big yellow box over
there Bobby or some I don't know
oh oh oh hold on everyone this
employee right down the aisle and I want
to go ask minute to see if there's any
sock on TVs in I know they we stock
every other week so I gotta make sure
just kind of find a place to put my
camera
and once that hey hey you yeah you
you get over here
yeah look up what's locked our DVD no
Sonic Underground it's a TV show
come on what no Tommy
on the ground you know the fiends loud
funny Underground Tommy on the ground
no no big what time do you know I do
what I walk I just watch TV
you got me give you my Feeny I'm gonna
be mad at huh can you believe it I just
peed in there
I should be your school no no no no no
no Rockets on up get Sonic you get his
little body and preach and you'll be
just smelly Alex your dog
[Music]